{
	"task" : [
		{
			"gameType" : "Affix",
			
			"questions" : [
				{ 	"question" : "any-",
					"answers" : [ "ja", ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "bé-",
					"answers" : [ "lyeg", ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "cser-",
					"answers" : [ "je", ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "pá-",
					"answers" : [ "lya", ],
				},
			],
			
			"answers" : [ "ja", "jeg", "lya", "lyeg", "je", "lya", "lye" ],
			
			"lifeNumber" : 0,
			"time" : 60,
		},

		{
			"gameType" : "Affix",
			
			"questions" : [
				{ 	"question" : "király",
					"answers" : [ "nő", "fi" ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "jeges",
					"answers" : [ "medve", ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "osztály",
					"answers" : [ "terem", "társ" ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "kulcs",
					"answers" : [ "lyuk", "tartó" ],
				},
			],
			
			"answers" : [ "nő", "tartó", "fi", "lyuk", "medve", "társ", "terem" ],

			"lifeNumber" : 0,
			"time" : 60,
		},

		{
			"gameType" : "Affix",
			
			"questions" : [
				{ 	"question" : "6, 8, 10",
					"answers" : [ "12", ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "7, 9, 11",
					"answers" : [ "13", ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "20, 30, 40",
					"answers" : [ "50", ],
				},
				{ 	"question" : "25, 50, 75",
					"answers" : [ "100", ],
				},
			],
			
			"answers" : [ "12", "50", "14", "95", "13", "65", "100" ],

			"lifeNumber" : 0,
			"time" : 60,
		},
	]
}